// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!


// Title: Netflix and Ill
module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What year did Netflix begin their DVD by mail service?', 
      a: '1994', 
      b: '1997',
      c: '2000',
      d: '2004',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What year did Netflix begin their streaming service?', 
      a: '2005', 
      b: '2007',
      c: '2009',
      d: '2011',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What was the first all-original show produced by Netflix?', 
      a: 'Orange is the New Black', 
      b: 'Chef\'s Table',
      c: 'Bojack Horseman',
      d: 'House of Cards',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What year did Blockbuster announce they would close all stores?', 
      a: '2006', 
      b: '2009',
      c: '2013',
      d: '2017',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many worldwide subscribers does Netflix have (as of 2020)?', 
      a: '61 Million', 
      b: '167 Million',
      c: '742 Million',
      d: '2.2 Billion',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What\'s the max number of devices that can stream from a Premium account at once?', 
      a: '4', 
      b: '10',
      c: '8',
      d: 'Unlimited',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What was Netflix\' annual revenue in 2019?', 
      a: '$984 Million', 
      b: '$1.1 Billion',
      c: '$10.2 Billion',
      d: '$20.2 Billion',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many Netflix Original serires and movies were released in 2019?', 
      a: '58', 
      b: '122',
      c: '229',
      d: '371',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'How did Netflix perform early user research in the late 90s?', 
      a: 'Public Access call in show', 
      b: 'In-home observation',
      c: 'ACN-led focus groups',
      d: 'Mail in questionairres',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the most streamed show on Netflix?', 
      a: 'Fuller House', 
      b: 'Friends',
      c: 'Stranger Things',
      d: 'The Office',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
};